WORLD OF TRUCKS – PRIVACY POLICY
================================

1\. PREAMBLE
------------

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| 1.1 | SCS Software s.r.o. with its registered office at Jihlavská 1558/21, Michle, 140 00 Praha 4, Czechia, Identification Number: 28181301, entered into Commercial Register maintained by the Prague City Court, Section C., Insert No. 131111(“Company”) operates a site called World of Trucks (“Site”) designed for users of the computer games developed by the Company (“Games”) where the users may share their experience with the Games and engage with other users to improve their Game experience. The purpose of this document is to provide users with information related to personal data processing in accordance with the requirements set out in Regulation (EU) 2016/679 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation, “GDPR”). |
| 1.2 | Any terms undefined in this document which are defined in GDPR shall have the same meaning as in GDPR. |

2\. SCOPE OF DATA PROCESSING
----------------------------

The Company acquires personal data related to the users of the Site upon their registration to the Site (and any subsequent updates of their user profiles) and / or in the course of their use of Games or the Site. In this respect, the Company processes in particular the following data:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| (a) | identification details of the users, such as name, nickname, login details, electronic address or social network identifiers; |
| (b) | data related to the Games usage such as routes driven, duration of playing or vehicles used (such data may be collected automatically as the users play the Games) or screenshots from the Games; |
| (c) | forum posts or chat messages; |

3\. PURPOSE OF DATA PROCESSING AND LEGAL BASIS
----------------------------------------------

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| 3.1 | The purpose of processing of personal data is to enable the Company to provide users with the services in accordance with the Terms of Service of the Site, i.e. under the contract with the users for the provision of services in relation to the Site. Personal data of users may also be processed for the purpose of ensuring compliance with the applicable laws, including audits or answering requests of public authorities. Such personal data processing is performed on the basis of Article 6 (1)(b) or (c) of the GDPR and therefore no consent of the user is necessary. |
| 3.2 | Provision of personal data for the purpose under Article 3.1 of this document is voluntary. However, without provision of such personal data the Company will not be able to provide the services featured on the Site to the user. Users also have the option to disable visibility of certain data (in particular data related to their use of the Games and / or the Site) to other users of the Site by selecting such option in their user profiles. |

4\. RECIPIENTS
--------------

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| 4.1 | The users acknowledge that the Company may make the above personal data available to other processors based on agreement with the Company (attorneys, accountants, salary accountants, auditors, tax and legal advisors, operators of virtual environment for the information system, etc.) to the extent necessary for carrying out their activities on the basis of their contract with the Company. |
| 4.2 | The above parties process the personal data on the basis of data processing agreement concluded with the Company and are not permitted to process personal data for other purposes than those set out above, unless required by applicable laws. |
| 4.3 | In an exceptional case when user‘s personal data are transferred outside of the European Economic Area, we will observe all respective requirements set out in the GDPR in order to ensure protection of such data, in particular, we will transfer them only to countries which were acknowledged by the European Commission as having adequate level of protection or personal data, or to parties who have appropriate safeguards in place (such as standard contractual clauses or binding corporate rules). |

5\. DURATION OF PROCESSING
--------------------------

The Company processes the personal data only for the time period necessary to fulfill the above purposes of data processing or as required by the applicable laws. After that all personal data are erased. Should the user delete his / her profile, the personal data are erased except (a) those that the Company is required to maintain by applicable laws and (b) public forum posts and chat messages which may however be erased upon request of the user based on the right to be forgotten under Article 6(c) below.

6\. RIGHTS OF THE USERS
-----------------------

In relation to the personal data provided to the Company, users have the following rights:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| (a) | Right of access: Each user shall have the right to obtain from the Company confirmation as to whether or not personal data concerning such user are being processed, and, where that is the case, to access such personal data and the related information, in particular concerning the purpose of personal data processing, its duration, categories of personal data processed and recipients to whom the personal data are disclosed. Such right to access may nevertheless be restricted based on the rights and freedoms of others. |
| (b) | Right to rectification: Upon request of the user, the Company shall correct inaccurate or amend incomplete personal data related to such user. |
| (c) | Right to erasure (Right to be forgotten): Under the conditions set out in GDPR, the Company shall, upon request of the user, erase the personal data for example in cases when such data are no longer necessary in relation to the purposes for which they were collected, they were processed based on the consent of user which was withdrawn, the user objected to their further processing or they were processed unlawfully. |
| (d) | Right to restrictions of processing: Under the conditions set out in GDPR (for example when the accuracy of personal data is contested by the user or the personal data were unlawfully processed), the Company shall, upon request of the user, restrict processing of personal data concerning such user; in such case the Company shall process such personal data only for limited reasons set out in GDPR or other applicable laws. |
| (e) | Right to data portability: Under the conditions set out in GDPR and to the extent of technical capabilities of the Company, users shall have right to receive the personal data they provided to the Company in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format and to transmit those data to another controller without hindrance from the Company. |
| (f) | Right to object: In certain cases the users may object to the processing of their personal data. In such case the Company may be required to cease from further processing of such personal data. |
| (g) | Right to withdraw consent: In case that the personal data of the user are processed based on his / her consent, the user shall have the right to withdraw such consent at any time in the same form and manner as the consent was originally given, or contact the Data Protection Officer for such purpose; lawfulness of personal data processing carried out prior to such withdrawal shall remain unaffected. |
| (h) | Right to contact the Data Protection Officer / Supervisory Authority: Users shall have right to contact Data Protection Officer at: [dataprotectionofficer@scssoft.com](mailto:dataprotectionofficer@scssoft.com) with inquiries and / or complaints regarding personal data processing. They shall also have the right to lodge a complaint with the Supervisory Authority (Czech Office for Protection of Personal Data). |

7\. COOKIES
-----------

7.1The Site uses cookies – small text files that are stored on user\`s web browser or device by web servers when the user visits some websites. Cookies are used to distinguish each user from other users of the website and to store data about use of the website (e.g. the number of site visitors, time spent visiting the website or what content interests the user).7.2This information is not linked to user‘s identity but rather to online identifiers (e.g. the type of browser used or the name of internet provider's domain) and is used to improve the Company\`s services and ensure the correct operation of the Site. The Company does not identify any individual Site visitors, unless they provide their contact details using the form(s) available on the Site.7.3The following types of cookies are used:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| (a) | **Strictly necessary cookies** (for example sid\_prod) – cookies that are required to ensure the correct operation of the Site. They include, for example, cookies that enable users to log into secure areas of the Site, use a shopping cart or make use of e-billing services; and |
| (b) | **Analytical/performance cookies** (for example Google Analytics – UA-44910654-1; \_ga, \_gat and \_gid) – They allow to recognise and count the number of visitors and to see how visitors move around the Site when they are using it. This helps to improve the way the Site works, for example, by ensuring that users find what they are looking for easily. |
| (c) | **Cookies for third-party embedded content** - cookies that are used to display third party content on the Site (such as YouTube videos). |

7.4Whether cookies are classified as "first-party" or "third-party" cookies depends on the domain that placed the cookies on user\`s web browser or device. First-party cookies are stored by the web server the user is visiting. Third-party cookies are cookies placed on user\`s device by a domain other than the website the user is currently on. The Company recently uses third-party cookies provided by Google, in particular Google Analytics for analysis of its Site traffic or YouTube cookies enabling to play videos on the Site. The privacy policy regarding such cookies can be found at:

[https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage)

7.5Persistent cookies are stored on user\`s device for a pre-defined amount of time. They are activated each time the user visits the web server which generated the respective cookie.7.6Session cookies allow website operators to link the actions of a user during a browser session. They are generated when the user accesses the website browser and are deleted when the users closes the browser.7.7All cookies except strictly necessary cookies may only be stored on user‘s device and processed with the user‘s consent. The user may grant / reject such consent in the pop-up window which is displayed upon first visit to the Site or anytime by clicking a link “Cookies Setting” at the bottom of the Site. The users can also change browser's cookie settings to allow or block cookies from being stored on their device. If the users decide to block cookies, they probably may not be able to fully use all functions of the Site.7.8The manner in which the user can enable/disable cookies is different for each browser. Specific instructions are provided under the browser’s “Help Menu”. More detailed information about cookie administration by the most commonly used web browsers is available here:

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| (a) | [Internet Explorer](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/278835/how-to-delete-cookie-files-in-internet-explorer) |
| (b) | [Firefox](http://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored) |
| (c) | [Chrome](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en&co=GENIE.Platform=Desktop) |
| (d) | [Opera](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/opera.html) |
| (e) | [Safari](https://support.apple.com/guide/safari/manage-cookies-and-website-data-sfri11471/mac) |
| (f) | [Safari for iPad a iPhone](http://support.apple.com/kb/HT1677) |
| (g) | [Microsoft Edge](https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/microsoft-edge/delete-cookies-in-microsoft-edge-63947406-40ac-c3b8-57b9-2a946a29ae09) |

7.9More information about cookies (including the administration and deletion of cookies) is available at: [www.allaboutcookies.org](https://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

**This document was last updated on December 28, 2021**  

[Support](https://www.worldoftrucks.com/en/support)[Terms of Service](https://www.worldoftrucks.com/en/terms)[Privacy Policy](https://www.worldoftrucks.com/en/privacy)[Cookie Settings](javascript:void(0);)[© 2024 SCS Software](https://scssoft.com/)
